Guide to the Francis Warrington Dawson Family Papers, 1386-1963, bulk 1859-1950 RL.10147
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Correspondence, 1859-1963 and undated
  - Browne, Lelia to [?], 1888 (Box 3)
  - Browne, S. T. to [?], 1888 (Box 3)
  - Broyles, A. to Dawson, F. W., 1887 (Box 3)
  - Bruce, Robert de to Dawson, Warrington, 1934 (Box 3)
  - Bruchesi, Jean to Dawson, Warrington, 1931-1932 (Box 3)
  - Bruneau, Charles to [?], 1931 (Box 3)
  - Bryan, G. W. to Morgan, Sarah, 1889 (Box 3)
  - Bryan, Isaac to Dawson, F. W., 1887 (Box 4)
  - Bryan, John S. to Dawson, Warrington, 1932-1934 (Box 4)
  - Bryan, M. to [?], 1914 (Box 4)
  - Bucklin, George to Dawson, Warrington, 1919 (Box 4)
  - Buell, Robert to Kelly, Robert, 1930 (Box 4)
  - Bull, S. to Dawson, Warrington, 1906 (Box 4)
  - Bullard, Ethel to various, 1932-1933 and undated (Box 4)
  - Bullitt, William to Dawson, Warrington, 1936 (Box 4)
  - Bumsel, Hyacinthe to Dawson, Warrington, 1931 (Box 4)
  - Bundy, Harvey to Edge, Walter, 1932 (Box 4)
  - Bunker, Frank to Dawson, Warrington, 1932 (Box 4)
  - Burdell, F. M. to [?], 1878 (Box 4)
  - Burger, Karl to Dawson, Warrington, 1939-1940 and undated (Box 4)
  - Burke, Charles to Dawson, Warrington, 1931 (Box 4)
  - Burleigh, Louise to Dawson, Warrington, 1921? (Box 4)
  - Burney, Minnie to Morgan, Sarah, 1889 (Box 4)
  - Burroughs, Ella to Dawson, F. W., 1874-1887 (Box 4)
  - Burroughs, Ella to Morgan, Sarah and [?], 1889-1894 (Box 4)
  - Burtnett, Bertrand to Dawson, Warrington, 1931 (Box 4)
  - Butler, E. J. to Middleton, 1932 (Box 4)
  - Butler, Nicholas to Dawson, Warrington, 1931 (Box 4)
  - Butler, W. C. to Dawson, F. W., 1879-1888 (Box 4)
  - Butts, Frances to Dawson, Warrington, 1931 (Box 4)
  - Byrne, John to Dawson, Warrington, 1920 (Box 4)
  - Byse, Mary to Dawson, Warrington, 1935 (Box 4)
  - Cabe, W. to Morgan, Sarah, 1889 (Box 4)
  - Cadoret, André to Dawson, Warrington, 1949 (Box 4)
  - Cadet, C. to [?], 1907 (Box 4)
  - Caffery, J. to Dawson, Warrington, 1931-1949 (Box 4)
  - Caldwell, Eleanor to Dawson, Warrington, 1930-1932 (Box 4)
  - Caldwell, L. to Dawson, Warrington, 1932-1933 (Box 4)
  - Caldwell, Mary to Morgan, Sarah, 1889 (Box 4)
  - Caldwell, [?] to Dawson, Warrington, undated (Box 4)
  - Calhoun, John C. to Nelson, Hugh, 1823 (Box 4)
  - Calhoun, William to Dawson, F. W., 1888 (Box 4)
  - Callison, James to Dawson, F. W., 1888 (Box 4)
  - Calvo, Charles to Morgan, Sarah, 1889 (Box 4)
  - Campbell, J. G. to Dawson, Warrington, 1945 (Box 4)
  - Cantelou Bros. to Dawson, Warrington, 1931 (Box 4)
  - Capitain, J. to [?], 1920 (Box 4)
  - Carey, Henry to Dawson, Warrington, 1916 (Box 4)
  - Carillon, Jeanne to Dawson, Warrington, 1932 (Box 4)
  - Carley, Mary to Dawson, F. W., 1888 (Box 4)
  - Carpenter, Richard to Dawson, F. W., 1886 (Box 4)
  - Carter, E. C. to Dawson, Warrington, 1919 (Box 4)
  - Carter, O. M. to Dawson, F. W., 1887 (Box 4)
  - Carter, William to [?], 1888 (Box 4)
  - Cary, [?] to Dawson, F. W., 1886 (Box 4)
  - Casanova, Jessie to various, 1933-1934 (Box 4)
  - Cash, Bogan to Dawson, F. W., 1888 (Box 4)
  - Casper-Jordan, Claude to [?], 1931 (Box 4)
  - Castle, William to [?], 1925 (Box 4)
  - Cathcart, W. R. to Dawson, Warrington, 1921 (Box 4)
  - Cauhépé, P. to [?], 1932 (Box 4)
  - Cavalier, A. to Dawson, Warrington, 1930 (Box 4)
  - Chack, Paul to Dawson, Warrington and [?], 1932 (Box 4)
  - Challamel, Augustin to Dawson, Warrington, 1918-1921 (Box 4)
  - Chamberlain, Daniel H. to Dawson, F. W., 1874-1888 (Box 4)
  - Chambon, Mme to [?], 1930 (Box 4)
  - Chambrun, Pierre to Dawson, Warrington, 1931 (Box 4)
  - Chandler, Edward to Dawson, Warrington, 1910 (Box 4)
  - Chandler, J. A. to Dawson, Warrington, 1931-1932 (Box 4)
  - Chapin, S. F. to Dawson, F. W., 1880s (Box 4)
  - Chapin, Vinton to Dawson, Warrington, 1935 (Box 4)
  - Chapman, C. C. to [?], 1889 (Box 4)
  - Charavay, Gabriel to [?], 1932 (Box 4)
  - Charleonnie, Germaine to Dawson, Warrington, 1930 (Box 4)
  - Charles, B. R. to Dawso, F. W., 1887-1888 (Box 4)
  - Charliat, P. to [?], 1932 (Box 4)
  - Charpentier, Jean to Romano and [?], 1931-1939 (Box 4)
  - Chatel, G. to Dawson, Warrington, 1932 (Box 4)
  - Chenoweth, Emma to various, 1931-1933 (Box 4)
  - Chenoweth, George to various, 1931-1932 (Box 4)
  - Cheremeteff, Serge to Dawson, Warrington, 1929-1930 (Box 4)
  - Chevrillon, André to Dawson, Warrington, 1946-1951 (Box 4)
  - Chilly, Josephine de to Dawson, Warrington, 1935 (Box 4)
  - Chilly, Munford to Dawson, Warrington, 1930-1933 (Box 4)
  - Chisolm, Mary to [?], 1889 (Box 4)
  - Christy, Gerald to Zangwill, 1912 (Box 4)
  - Clairouin, Ilenyse to Dawson, Warrington?, 1927-1933 (Box 4)
  - Clavaret, J. to Dawson, Warrington, 1932 (Box 4)
  - Clark, A. to Dawson, Warrington, 1914 (Box 4)
  - Clark, C. Cooper to [?], 1888 (Box 4)
  - Clemens, Cyril to Dawson, Warrington, 1948 (Box 4)
  - Clerk, William to Dawson, Warrington, 1937 (Box 4)
  - Childs, W. to Dawson, F. W., 1888 (Box 5)
  - Clermont, Marius to Dawson, Warrington, 1932 (Box 5)
  - Cleveland, [?] to Morgan, Sarah, 1899 (Box 5)
  - Clift, James to Segonne, Lilian, 1931 (Box 5)
  - Clugston, Paul to various, 1946-1954 (Box 5)
  - Cluzeau, J. Origet du to Drouot, M., 1947 (Box 5)
  - Cobb, C. H. to Dawson, Warrington, 1931 (Box 5)
  - Cobb, S. to Dawson, Warrington, 1922-1931 (Box 5)
  - Cocke, Jack to various, 1930 (Box 5)
  - Cocke, Jack to Dawson, Warrington, 1926-1934 and undated (Box 5)
  - Coffey, Edmond to various, 1932-1933 (Box 5)
  - Coffey, Evelyn to Dawson, Warrington, 1933 (Box 5)
  - Coffin, Robert A. to [?], 1883 (Box 5)
  - Coghill, Harvie to Wood, J. B., 1921 (Box 5)
  - Coghill, Harvie to Dawson, Warrington, 1921-1932 (Box 5)
  - Cogswell, Francis to Dawson, Warrington, 1956 (Box 5)
  - Cohen, C. to Dawson, Warrington, 1928; 1 folders (Box 5)
  - Cole, Felix to various, 1930-1931; 1 folders (Box 5)
  - Cole, Jas. To McKissick, E. P., 1889; 1 folders (Box 5)
  - Collins, Victor to Dawson, Warrington, 1920; 1 folders (Box 5)
  - Collins, V. Lansing to Dawson, Warrington, 1931-1932 (Box 5)
  - Colver, F. to [?], 1888 (Box 5)
  - Conant, Samuel to Dawson, Warrington, 1931 (Box 5)
  - Condon, Evelyn to Dawson, Warrington, 1931-1932 (Box 5)
  - Condrey, Ruth to [?], 1931? (Box 5)
  - Conquest, Edwin to Dawson, Warrington, 1931 (Box 5)
  - Conrad, Borys to Dawson, Warrington, 1911-1912 (Box 5)
  - Conrad, Jessie to Dawson, Warrington, 1911-1936 and undated; 3 folders (Box 5)
  - Conrad, Joseph to Dawson, Warrington, 1910-1929 and undated; 2 folders (Box 5)
  - Conte, Renée le to Dawson, Warrington, 1935 (Box 5)
  - Converse, [?] to Dawson, Warrington, 1932 (Box 5)
  - Corbett, John to Morgan, Sarah, 1889 (Box 5)
  - Corbett, John to [?], 1887 (Box 5)
  - Corcoran, Jas. To Morgan, Sarah, 1889 (Box 5)
  - Cordier, Henry to [?], 1932 (Box 5)
  - Cordingley, Nora to Dawson, Warrington, 1930-1946 (Box 5)
  - Corwick, Robert to Dawson, Warrington and [?], 1905-1906 (Box 5)
  - Cosgrove, James to [?], 1887 (Box 5)
  - Cotchett, W. V. to Dawson, Warrington, 1931 (Box 5)
  - Coutte, Paul to Dawson, Warrington, 1931 (Box 5)
  - Couklin, M. T. to Dawson, Warrington, 1910 (Box 5)
  - Couvreur, Paul to Dawson, Warrington, 1931 (Box 5)
  - Cox, L. B. to [?], 1888 (Box 5)
  - Coxe, H. C. to Dawson, Warrington, 1930 (Box 5)
  - Craster, H. H. E. to Dawson, Warrington, 1931 (Box 5)
  - Crawford, Andrew to Bolga, H. L. P., 1896 (Box 5)
  - Crawford, W. H. to General Lafayette, 1822 (Box 5)
  - Crequi, Marquis de to [?], 1939 (Box 5)
  - Creveaux, Maurice to Dawson, Warrington, 1939 (Box 5)
  - Crompton, Richer to Dawson, Warrington, 1932 (Box 5)
  - Cronly & Morris to News & Courier, 1888 (Box 5)
  - Crosscup & West to Dawson, F. W., 1888 (Box 5)
  - Crowe, Helen to Dawson, Warrington, 1931 (Box 5)
  - Crutcher, Anne to Dawson, Warrington, 1931 (Box 5)
  - Cudebec, Albert to Dawson, Warrington, 1931-1932 (Box 5)
  - Cuers, Andrée de to [?], 1930-1934 (Box 5)
  - Cunningham, Robert to Dawson, Warrington and [?], 1945 (Box 6)
  - Curtis, Bessie to Dawson, Warrington, 1932 (Box 6)
  - Dabbs, E. W. to Dawson, F. W., 1888 (Box 6)
  - Dabija, Paul Coze to Dawson, Warrington, 1934 (Box 6)
  - Daltour, Bulah to Dawson, Warrington, 1931 (Box 6)
  - D'Ambléon, L. to various, 1932 and undated (Box 6)
  - Dargan, John to Dawson, F. W., 1887 (Box 6)
  - D'Argenson, Marquis to [?], 1938 (Box 6)
  - Dargon, G. W. to Dawson, F. W., 1888 (Box 6)
  - Darier, M. to [?], 1889-1900 and undated (Box 6)
  - Darr, H. L. to Dawson, F. W., 1888 (Box 6)
  - Darreau, J. to Dawson, Warrington, 1909 (Box 6)
  - D'Ars, André to Dawson, Warrington, undated (Box 6)
  - Daste, Marie-Hélène to [?], 1948-1949 (Box 6)
  - Daudet, Lucien to [?], 1913 (Box 6)
  - Dausereau, Muriel to Dawson, Warrington, 1935 (Box 6)
  - Daves, Graham to Dawson, F. W., 1888 (Box 6)
  - David Kimball & Co. to Morgan, Sarah, 1890 (Box 6)
  - Davies, Marian to Dawson, Warrington, undated (Box 6)
  - Davies, Morgan to Dawson, Warrington, 1934 (Box 6)
  - Davies, A. G. to Dawson, Warrington, 1932 (Box 6)
  - Davis, Mary to Dawson, Warrington, 1934 (Box 6)
  - Davis, R. to Dawson, F. W., 1889 (Box 6)
  - Davis, Robert to Dawson, Warrington, 1931-1933 (Box 6)
  - Davray, Henry to Dawson, Warrington, 1922 (Box 6)
  - Dawbarn, Charles to Dawson, Warrington, 1922 (Box 6)
  - Dawson, Charles to Dawson, Warrington, 1931 (Box 6)
  - Dawson, Dallas to Dawson, F. W., 1888 (Box 6)
  - Dawson, Ethel to Dawson, F. W., 1886 (Box 6)
  - Dawson, F. W. to Morgan, J. M., 1875 (Box 6)
  - Dawson, F. W. to Jem (James Morris Morgan), 1875 (Box 6)
  - Dawson, F. W. to Mother and/or Father, 1862-1868 (Box 6)
  - Dawson, F. W. to Mother and/or Sister, 1866 (Box 6)
  - Dawson, F. W. with Morgan, Sarah, 1873; 3 folders (Box 6)
  - Dawson, F. W. to Morgan, Sarah, 1873-1880s; 5 folders (Box 6)
  - Dawson, F. W. to Morgan, Sarah and/or children, 1882-1889; 5 folders (Box 7)
  - Dawson, F. W. to multiple recipients- letterpress, 1879-1887; 2 folders (Box 32)
    Scope and Contents note
    Letterpress book of correspondence with multiple recipients (mostly professional); highly fading; multiple handwritings suggest secretary
  - Dawson, F. W. to Whitney, 1862 (Box 7)
  - Dawson, F. W. to various, 1860s-1888 and undated; 2 folders (Box 7)
  - Dawson, J. C. to Dawson, Warrington, 1931 (Box 7)
  - Dawson, Riordan to [?], 1873 (Box 7)
  - Dawson, Warrington to various, 1909-1963 and undated; 47 folders (Box 7)
    Includes telegrams.
  - Dawson, Warrington to [?], 1903 (Box 11)
  - Daymont, L. J. to Dawson, Warrington, 1945 (Box 11)
  - Dayot, Armand to [?], 1918 and undated (Box 11)
  - D'Azy, Charles de Behoist to [?], 1939 (Box 11)
  - D'Chaveau, [?] to Dawson, Warrington, 1931 (Box 11)
  - Dearman, Noah to Dawson, Warrington, undated (Box 11)
  - Debien, G. to [?], undated (Box 11)
  - Decou, Filix to Dawson, Warrington, 1914 (Box 11)
  - De Lauseure, Frannie to [?], 1889 (Box 11)
  - De Leon, Agnes to Morgan, Sarah, 1889 (Box 11)
  - De Leon, J. C. to Dawson, F. W., 1887 (Box 11)
  - Demour, Maryse to [?], 1934 (Box 11)
  - Denis, Fernand to Dawson, Warrington, 1931 (Box 11)
  - Dennery, E. to Thomas, Marcelle, 1947 (Box 11)
  - Derby, Ethel to Dawson, Warrington, 1919 (Box 11)
  - Derby, George to Barry, Herbert, 1932 (Box 11)
  - Derby, George to Dawson, Warrington, 1930 (Box 11)
  - Derby, Richard to Dawson, Warrington, 1919 (Box 11)
  - Desjean, E. to various, 1937 (Box 11)
  - DeTreville, James to Dawson, Warrington, 1933 (Box 11)
  - Devereaux, J. to Dawson, F. W., 1888 (Box 11)
  - Dewey, Stoddard to Dawson, Warrington, 1929 (Box 11)
  - Dial, N. B. to Morgan, Sarah, 1889 (Box 11)
  - Dibble, Samuel to Dawson, F. W., 1886-1888 (Box 11)
  - Dickinson, Don to Dawson, F. W., 1887 (Box 11)
  - Dickinson, Edward to Dawson, F. W., 1888 (Box 11)
  - Dickinson, Eileen to Dawson, Warrington, 1926 (Box 11)
  - Dillon, Comte to [?], 1931-1932 (Box 11)
  - Dollfus, Genevieve to Dawson, Warrington, 1930-1931 and undated (Box 11)
  - Donaldson, John to Dawson, Warrington, 1916 (Box 11)
  - Donghi, Frank to Dawson, Warrington, 1947 (Box 11)
  - Donohue, James to Dawson, Warrington, 1935 (Box 11)
  - Douglas, K. to Dawson, Warrington, 1922 (Box 11)
  - D'Ovres, Etinne to [?], undated (Box 12)
  - Doyle, O. M. to Morgan, Sarah, 1889 (Box 12)
  - Drake, Francis to Dawson, Warrington, 1932 (Box 12)
  - Drum, Lavinia to Dunkin, Eunice, 1902-1909 (Box 12)
  - Drum, Lavinia to Morgan, Sarah, 1888-1909; 2 folders (Box 12)
  - Drum, Lavinia to Dawson, Warrington, 1901-1910 (Box 12)
  - Drum, R. C. to Zay, 1897 (Box 12)
  - Drummond, Mae to Dawson, Warrington, 1913-1922 (Box 12)
  - Dubos, Bernard to [?], 1932 (Box 12)
  - Duchein, Laura to Dawson, Warrington, undatd (Box 12)
  - Duchein, Scott to Dawson, Warrington, 1931 (Box 12)
  - Duchenne, Achille to Rockefeller, 1931 (Box 12)
  - Duchesse de Rohan to Dawson, Warrington, 1925 (Box 12)
  - Ducrocq, Albert to Dawson, Warrington, 1953 (Box 12)
  - Duell, Prentice to Dawson, Warrington, 1936 (Box 12)
  - Duffy, P. L. to Dawson, F. W., 1886 (Box 12)
  - Duffy, P. L. to Morgan, Sarah, 1889 (Box 12)
  - Dukes, Alice to Dawson, Warrington, 1911-1912 (Box 12)
  - Dulles, Allen W. to Dawson, Warrington, 1920-1930 (Box 12)
  - Dumas, J. Edward to [?], 1931 (Box 12)
  - Dumay, Henri to Dawson, Warrington, 1922 (Box 12)
  - Duncan, B. to Dawson, F. W., 1888 (Box 12)
  - Duncan, D. R. to Dawson, F. W., 1887-1888 and undated (Box 12)
  - Duphot, Cécile to Dawson, Warrington, 1909-1922 and undated (Box 12)
  - Du Pont, A. F. to Dawson, Warrington, 1932 (Box 12)
  - Durillers, A. to [?], 1931 (Box 12)
  - Dwight, H. G. to Dawson, Warrington, 1931 (Box 12)
  - Earle, Jos H. to Dawson, F. W., 1886-1888 (Box 12)
  - Earle, William to Dawson, F. W., 1888 (Box 12)
  - Eastman, Ralph to Shurtleff, Harold, 1931 (Box 12)
  - Edes, Robert to Dawson, Warrington, 1920-1921 and undated (Box 12)
  - Edgerton, David to [?], 1915 (Box 12)
  - Edgerton, Jas to Dawson, F. W., 1888 (Box 12)
  - Edwards, B. W. to Dawson, F. W., 1888 (Box 12)
  - Eggimann, Ch. To Dawson, Warrington, 1932 (Box 12)
  - Eggleston, J. D. to Hayes, Elizabeth, 1933 (Box 12)
  - Ellett, Thomas to Dawson, F. W., 1888 (Box 12)
  - Ellyson, H. K. to Dawson, F. W., 1887-1888 (Box 12)
  - Ely, Robert to Dawson, Warrington, 1910 (Box 12)
  - Erappe, Georges to Dawson, Warrington, 1912 (Box 12)
  - Erickson, Gus to Dawson, Warrington, 1941 (Box 12)
  - Ermida, Carlos R. to Colson, Eugène, 1939 (Box 12)
  - Erwin, J. M. to Dawson, Warrington, 1934 (Box 12)
  - Escande, P. to Dawson, Warrington, 1939 (Box 12)
  - Eshinger, Ernest to Dawson, Warrington, undated (Box 12)
  - Estill, J. H. to Dawson, F. W., 1888 (Box 12)
  - Ethridge, J. to Dawson, Warrington, 1947 (Box 12)
  - Euvé, R. to Dawson, Warrington, 1939 (Box 12)
  - Evans, J. to [?], 1912 (Box 12)
  - Evans, L. H. to Moroes, J. A., 1889 (Box 12)
  - Everhart, Lay to various, 1931-1932 (Box 12)
  - Fabert, Jean to Dawson, Warrington, 1931 (Box 12)
  - Fangel, Lisa to [?], 1889 (Box 12)
  - Farish, Hunter D. to Dawson, Warrington, 1939 (Box 12)
  - Farland, A. to Dawson, Warrington, 1921 (Box 12)
  - Farrell, Frank to Dawson, F. W., 1887 (Box 12)
  - Feakins, William to Dawson, Warrington, 1909-1910 (Box 12)
  - Fehr, H. to Dawson, Warrington, 1931 (Box 12)
  - Ferguson, J. S. to Morgan, Sarah, 1889 (Box 12)
  - Ferguson, John to Morgan, Sarah, 1889 (Box 12)
  - Ferguson, Thelma to Dawson, Warrington, 1935 (Box 12)
  - Ferrall, Leon to Morgan, Sarah, 1893 (Box 12)
  - Field, William to Dawson, Warrington, 1912-1913 (Box 12)
  - Figuière, Eugène to [?], 1925 (Box 12)
  - Fillion, Joshua to [?], 1909 (Box 12)
  - Fincke, Fred to [?], 1889 (Box 12)
  - Finot, Jean to [?], 1921-1922 (Box 12)
  - Fisher, Mary to Dawson, Warrington, 1931 (Box 12)
  - Flack, Joseph to Dawson, Warrington, 1921 (Box 12)
  - Flammarion, Camille to Dawson, Warrington?, 1914-1930 and undated (Box 12)
  - Flammarion, Sylvie to Dawson, Warrington, 1902 (Box 12)
  - Fleming, F. P. to Morgan, Sarah, 1891 (Box 12)
  - Fleury, Serge to Dawson, Warrington, 1929-1930 (Box 12)
  - Fleury, Serge to [?], 1931 and undated (Box 12)
  - Follereau, Raoul to Dawson, Warrington, 1932-1933 (Box 12)
  - Follmer, Cyrus to Dawson, Warrington, 1945 (Box 12)
  - Fontana, P. to Dawson, Warrington, 1922 (Box 12)
  - Fontenelle, Page de to Dawson, Warrington, 1930-1939 (Box 12)
  - Foran, W. Robert to Roosevelt, Kermit, 1921 (Box 12)
  - Foran, W. Robert to Dawson, Warrington, 1909-1910 (Box 12)
  - Forbes, G. to Dawson, Warrington, 1930-1932 (Box 13)
  - Ford, Grace to Morgan, Sarah, 1889 (Box 13)
  - Ford, H. C. to Dawson, Warrington, 1919 (Box 13)
  - Ford, Stanley to various, 1931-1932 (Box 13)
  - Ford, Worthington to Dawson, Warrington, 1930-1932 (Box 13)
  - Foutannag, S. to [?], 1889 (Box 13)
  - Fowler, Dauphine to Morgan, Sarah, 1889 (Box 13)
  - Fowler, P. R. to Morgan, Sarah, 1889 (Box 13)
  - Fox, Robert to Dawson, Warrington, 1932 (Box 13)
  - Fraikin, Gérard to Dawson, Warrington, 1932 (Box 13)
  - Francheterse, Y. to Dawson, Warrington, 1938 (Box 13)
  - Francia, J. de to Dawson, Warrington, 1930 (Box 13)
  - Frank, Augustus to Dawson, Warrington, 1931 (Box 13)
  - Frank, Victor to Dawson, Warrington, 1932 (Box 13)
  - Franklin, Clarence Payne to Watson, 1910 (Box 13)
  - Frazier, W. Hugh to Dawson, Warrington, 1921 (Box 13)
  - Friedel, [?] to [?], 1906 (Box 13)
  - Frost, Donald to Dawson, Warrington, 1921-1931 (Box 13)
  - Fullerton, Hugh S. to various, 1947 (Box 13)
  - Fullerton, Morton to various, 1921-1931 (Box 13)
  - Fullerton, W. M. to [?], 1930-1932 (Box 13)
  - Furst, Henry to Dawson, Warrington, 1931 (Box 13)
  - Furst, W. S. to Edge, Walter, 1931 (Box 13)
  - Fuster, Charles to [?], 1912? (Box 13)
  - Gabbitas, Thring, & Co. to Dawson, Warrington, 1932 (Box 13)
  - Galenousha, M. to [?], 1931-1932 (Box 13)
  - Gallatin, Albert to Duke of San Lorenzo, 1823 (Box 13)
  - Gallatin, Albert ot Dawson, Warrington, 1931-1934 (Box 13)
  - Galphin, Margaret to Dawson, Warrington, 1932 (Box 13)
  - Gallatin, Marie-Lucile de to Dawson, Warrington, 1930-1931 (Box 13)
  - Galopin, Arnould to [?], 1931 (Box 13)
  - Gallyfy, G. to [?], 1902 (Box 13)
  - Gammet, L. to Dawson, Warrington, 1931-1935 (Box 13)
  - Gardener, Helen to Morgan, Sarah, 1889 (Box 13)
  - Gardner, Walter to various, 1932-1934 (Box 13)
  - Garnier, L. to [?] to [?], 1947 (Box 13)
  - Garvan, Francis to Dawson, Warrington, 1921 (Box 13)
  - Gatty, Alfred Scott to Dawson, F. W., 1885 (Box 13)
  - Gaubert, R. C. to Dawson, Warrington, 1945 (Box 13)
  - Gayle, Builah to Dawson, Warrington, 1931 (Box 13)
  - Gayle, Sarah to [?], 1932 (Box 13)
  - Gebinotte, W. to Dawson, Warrington and [?], 1918-1919 (Box 13)
  - Geddes, Chas to White, Blake, 1889 (Box 13)
  - Geddy, V. M. to Dawson, Warrington, 1932 (Box 13)
  - Gédéon, Léon to Dawson, Warrington, 1949 (Box 13)
  - Geiger, William to Morgan, Sarah, 1889 (Box 13)
  - Gibbes, Sallie to Morgan, Sarah, 1889 (Box 13)
  - Gibbons, Herbert to various, 1929 (Box 13)
  - Gibbons, Herbert to Dawson, Warrington, 1918-1934 (Box 13)
  - Gibson, Hugh to Dawson, Warrington, 1920-1940 and undated (Box 13)
  - Gilmer, Albert to various, 1934 (Box 13)
  - Gizodie, André to [?], 1930-1931 (Box 13)
  - Glass, W. C. to Dawson, Warrington, 1909-1910 (Box 13)
  - Glidden, C. H. to Dawson, F. W., 1886 and undated (Box 13)
  - Goncourt, J. de to [?], 1950 (Box 13)
  - Gonzales, W. E. to Dawson, F. W., 1888 (Box 13)
  - Goodreds, H. to Barry, Stuyvesant, 1953 (Box 13)
  - Goodwin, Mary to Dawson, Warrington, 1929-1931 and undated (Box 13)
  - Goodwin, T. Rutherfoord to Dawson, Warrington, 1931-1939 (Box 13)
  - Goodwin, W. A. R. to Dawson, Warrington, 1929-1949 (Box 13)
  - Goodwin, W. A. R. to various, 1930-1932 (Box 13)
  - Gordon, George to Dawson, Warrington, 1921-1930 (Box 13)
  - Gordon, Geroge to [?], 1922 (Box 13)
  - Gormaud, Hélène to [?], undated (Box 13)
  - Gough, John to Dawson, Warrington, 1931-1936 (Box 13)
  - Gournay, J. de to Dawson, Warrington, 1930 (Box 13)
  - Grady, H. to Dawson, F. W., 1887 (Box 13)
  - Graham, C. to Dawson, F. W., 1888-1889 (Box 13)
  - Graham, James to Dawson, F. W., 1888 (Box 13)
  - Graindorge, P.H. to Dawson, Warrington, 1949 (Box 13)
  - Granger, Doreen to various, 1932-1933 (Box 13)
  - Grant, M. S. to Dawson, Warrington, 1931 (Box 13)
  - Green, Alice to Dawson, Warrington, 1911-1924 and undated (Box 13)
  - Green, Julian to Dawson, Warrington, undated (Box 13)
  - Greene, G. A. B. to [?], 1889 (Box 14)
  - Greffulhe, Comtesse to Dawson, Warrington, 1933 (Box 14)
  - Gresse, Marquis de to Dawson, Warrington, 1931-1933 (Box 14)
  - Grew, Joseph to various, 1926 (Box 14)
  - Griffith, Robert to Dawson, Warrington, 1925 (Box 14)
  - Grinnell, Robert to Dawson, Warrington, 1950 (Box 14)
  - Griscom, Lloyd to Dawson, Warrington, 1909 (Box 14)
  - Grossier, Edmond to Dawson, Warrington, 1930 (Box 14)
  - Grundy, F. B. to Dawson, Warrington, 1910-1931 (Box 14)
  - Guerreau, Henri to Dawson, Warrington, 1921-1926 (Box 14)
  - Guggenheim, David to Dawson, F. W., 1888 (Box 14)
  - Guichen, Vicomte de to [?], 1932 (Box 14)
  - Guilaine, L. to Dawson, Warrington?, 1921 (Box 14)
  - Guilday, Peter to [?], 1933 (Box 14)
  - Guillain, J. to Dawson, Warrington, 1932 (Box 14)
  - Gunnell, David to Morgan, Sarah, 1889 (Box 14)
  - Gunther, E. L. to Dulles, 1921 (Box 14)
  - Hackett, Beatrice to Dawson, Warrington, 1921-1927 and undated (Box 14)
  - Hackett, James to Dawson, Warrington, 1921-1922 (Box 14)
  - Hackett, James to various, 1926 (Box 14)
  - Hagedorn, Hermann to Dawson, Warrington, 1924-1927 (Box 14)
  - Hagen, [?] to [?], 1931? (Box 14)
  - Hagood, Johnson to [?], 1888 (Box 14)
  - Hale, R. T. to Dawson, Warrington, 1909-1926 (Box 14)
  - Hall, Jeannette to Dawson, Warrington, 1921-1932 (Box 14)
  - Hall, Maurice to Dawson, Warrington, 1931-1932 (Box 14)
  - Hallard, A. to Dawson, Warrington, 1921-1926 and undated (Box 14)
  - Hallock, H. G. C. to [?], 1927-1929 (Box 14)
  - Hallowell, H. to Dawson, Warrington, 1926 (Box 14)
  - Hallowes, L. M. to Dawson, Warrington, 1923-1924 (Box 14)
  - Halsey, R. T. H. to Goodwin, W. A. R., 1931 (Box 14)
  - Halshad, Albert to various, 1919-1920 (Box 14)
  - Hamilton, J. Stuart to Dawson, Warrington, 1925-1926 (Box 14)
  - Hampton, P. L. to Dawson, F. W., 1888 (Box 14)
  - Hanckel, W. J. to Morgan, Sarah, 1889 (Box 14)
  - Handy, Egbert to various, 1932 (Box 14)
  - Hanna, A. J. to Dawson, Warrington, 1931-1934 (Box 14)
  - Hanner, E. A. to Snowden, 1889 (Box 14)
  - Harding, Julia to Dawson, Warrington, 1913-1932 (Box 14)
  - Harding, Lavinia to Morgan, Sarah, 1889 (Box 14)
  - Harding, Morgan to Dawson, Warrington, 1931 (Box 14)
  - Hare, Florence to Dawson, Warrington, undated (Box 14)
  - Harlan, E. R. to Dawson, Warrington, 1914 (Box 14)
  - Harmati, Sandor to Dawson, Warrington, 1931 (Box 14)
  - Harrison, Alexander to [?], undated (Box 14)
  - Harrison, Constance to Dawson, Warrington, 1905-1910 and undated (Box 14)
  - Harrison, Leland to Herrick, Myron, 1926 (Box 14)
  - Harrison, Leland to Dawson, Warrington, 1937 (Box 14)
  - Hart, Harold to Dawson, Warrington, 1919 (Box 14)
  - Harts, William to Dawson, Warrington, 1929 (Box 14)
  - Harvey, W. to Dawson, Warrington, 1931 (Box 14)
  - Harvey, Wilson to Dawson, Warrington, 1923 (Box 14)
  - Haskell, A. C. to Dawson, F. W., 1887 (Box 14)
  - Haskell, A. C. to Morgan, Sarah, 1892 (Box 14)
  - Haskell, Dudley to Dawson, Warrington, 1932-1935 (Box 14)
  - Haskell, Edwin to Dawson, Warrington, 1931 (Box 14)
  - Haskell, J. C. to Dawson, F. W., 1888 (Box 14)
  - Haskell, John to Dawson, F. W., 1887 (Box 14)
  - Hastings-Jones, F. to Dawson, Warrington, 1921-1932 and undated (Box 14)
  - Hawkins, Eric to Dawson, Warrington, 1931 (Box 14)
  - Haye, Henry to various, 1939 (Box 14)